{"description":"A set of questions to test the software with","name":"Loadmaster Airdrop (May 18)","version":1,"questions":[{"question":"101. If ADS Rail Locks are _____ before lock force pounds are set, false\/inaccurate force pounds settings may result.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -7 (W)]","responses":["locked","unlocked","tested","armed"]},{"question":"102. The Depressurization Checklist will be run prior to the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -203]","responses":["Pre -Slowdown checklist.","Slowdown checklist.","Release Point","1 minute warning"]},{"question":"103. Accomplish the Cabin Altitude Checklist before _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -201]","responses":["the Pre-Slowdown Checklist","the Slowdown Checklist","exceeding a cabin altitude of 10,000 feet MSL","exceeding a cabin altitude of 12,5000 feet MSL."]},{"question":"104. If the drogue chute does not deploy automatically or with the manual backup switch, the loadmaster will state _____ and complete the Heavy Equipment Malfunction Checklist.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -38]","responses":["\"NO DROP\"","\"MALFUNCTION\"","\"DROGUE JETTISONED\"","\"JETTISON MALFUNCTION\""]},{"question":"105. If the Tow Release Mechanism fails to release the extraction link (either automatically or with the manual backup switch), the loadmaster will state, \u201cMALFUNCTION\u201d and activate the DROGUE JETTISON switch. If the drogue fails to jettison, the loadmaster will _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -42]","responses":["state \"JETTISON MALFUNCTION\"","activate the EMERG DROGUE Jettison switch","activate the R LOCKS GANG RELEASE switch","place the DROGUE JETTISON switch to the OFF position"]},{"question":"106. If the extraction parachutes have exited the aircraft and the platform fails to move, ensure the _____ rotary switch is set to the lowest lock number setting that is engaged in the platform\t \t that failed to move and activate the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -44]","responses":["CDS GATE SELECT; ADS BACKUP CDS Switch","DROP GP SELECT; R LOCKS GANG RELEASE switch","ADS R LOCK SELECT; R LOCKS GANG RELEASE switch","ADS L LOCK SELECT; L LOCKS GANG RELEASE switch"]},{"question":"107. The C -17 has the capability to airdrop a total of _____ pounds using multiple Type V airdrop platforms with the EFTC.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 1 -78]","responses":["60,000","110,000","50,000","90,000"]},{"question":"108. The maximum dimensions of airdrop loads are _____ inches high measured from the bottom of the platform\t and _____ inches wide.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 1 -79]","responses":["118; 126","118; 108","126; 118","101; 126"]},{"question":"109. When additional personnel airdrops are conducted after the initial airdrop sorti e, loadmasters shall reinspect the troop doors before takeoff IAW the Personnel Airdrop Preparation and Loading Checklist. For subsequent personnel airdrops, a tactile -only check is required between drops.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -111]","responses":["TRUE","FALSE"]},{"question":"110. During a towed parachutist condition, the PF will _____ as the parachutist may start swinging violently, which will increase the possibility of injury.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -9]","responses":["avoid turning the aircraft in the direction of the towed parachutist","initiate a steep climb","turn the aircraft in the direction of the towed parachutist","increase airspeed"]},{"question":"111. During a towed parachutist condition, if the decision to cut t he parachutist free, the _____ will cut the static line on the aircraft commander \u2019s command.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -12]","responses":["Jumpmaster","Safety Personnel","Mission Commander","Loadmaster"]},{"question":"112. During Fouled Parachutist Retrieval do not attempt to pull the _____ through the spool assembly.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -19 (W)]","responses":["personnel","D-bags ","yoke assembly","all of the above"]},{"question":"113. During the CDS Airdrop Slowdown Checklist, visually inspect each Type XXVI nylon release gate to ensure it is positioned on the GRM release roller and _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -137 (N)]","responses":["that all the excess webbing folded and taped","the looped end overlaps the release arm hinge joint","has not become tangled or caught on the release arm hinge joint","the Van Zelm ratchets are tightened to the maximum extent possible"]},{"question":"114. If the GRM(s) fail to release or the load stops moving aft, the loadmaster will state _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 4 -49]","responses":["\"NO DROP\" and attempt to secure any loose containers","\"LOAD CLEAR\" after all containers that are moving have exited","\"MALFUNCTION\" and attempt to secure any moving containers","\"MALFUNCTION\" after all containers that are moving have exited"]},{"question":"115. Loadmasters requiring mobility in the cargo compartment while using a restraint harness can be unattached as long as they remain forward of _____ with the cargo door and ramp open or with the\t_____ paratroop door(s) open.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 19.5.2.1E]","responses":["FS 1165; FS 1074","FS 1188; FS 1027","FS 1309; FS 1092","FS 1403; FS 1135"]},{"question":"116. For static line jumps, static lines are attached to anchor cables before troop door(s) are opened. Jumpers exiting on subsequent passes may stand and hook up with door(s) opened if they are forward of _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"11 -2C -17 V3 [Para. 19.5.2E]","responses":["FS 781","FS 1027 ","FS 1100 ","FS 1188"]},{"question":"117. When in-flight rigging is required, the loadmaster will use the applicable _____ as a checklist to ensure all items are completed.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -92]","responses":["rigging manual","section of the loading manual","section of the airdrop manual","Joint Airdrop Inspection Form"]},{"question":"118. A \"No Drop\" will be called if Slowdown or Quick Drop checklist items are not completed prior to the initiation of the _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -103 (N)]","responses":["Cabin Altitude Checklist","Malfunction Checklist","Release Point Checklist","Post Drop Checklist"]},{"question":"119. Loadmasters may attempt to regain ADS logic up to initiation of the _____ checklist.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":1,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -104]","responses":["Slowdown","Release point","Pre-slowdown","none of the above"]},{"question":"120. When preflighting the retriever winch cable for personnel airdrops, up to _____ broken wires are allowed per inch . The maximum number of broken wires shall not occur in any two consecutive inches of cable.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":2,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -4]","responses":["0","2","3","6 "]},{"question":"121. In the event that a lock is engaged in a platform and the second lock on the same panel is engaged between, adjacent or aft of the platform, use the INC\/DECR toggle switch and decrease the setting _____.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":3,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -7]","responses":["below 500 lbs","one increment below the required restraint","until the lock releases","to 00 for a minimum of 2 seconds "]},{"question":"122. The required number of left hand locks engaged in each platform must be equal to or greater than the number of right hand locks engaged in that platform.","type":"multiple_choice","correct_response":0,"ref":"TO 1C -17A -1 -4 [Para. 2 -7 (N)]","responses":["TRUE","FALSE"]}]}
